A Guide to the William M. Dietel papers FA1142
Rockefeller Archive Center
William M. Dietel papers
1969-1970, 1973-1996
Rockefeller Archive Center
Dietel, William M.
FA1142
37.05 Cubic Feet 78 letter document boxes, 7 legal document boxes, 1 half document box
Arrangement
Arranged by Accession.
Accession 1
Accession 2
Accession 3
Scope and Contents
Type of records include: Reports, publications, newspaper articles, correspondence, and reprints
Biographical / Historical
William Morse Dietel is a graduate of Princeton University with a M. A. and Yale University with a Ph.D. He taught history at the University of Massachusetts and was an associate professor of the humanities at Amherst College, where he also served as assistant dean of the college. From 1961 to 1970 he was principal of the Emma Willard School in Troy, New York. Then in 1970 he joined the Rockefeller Brothers Fund, where he became the President in 1975-1987.
Mr. Dietel has had extensive experience as a board member and officer of a broad array of nonprofit organizations, including the New York Public Library, Colonial Williamsburg Foundation, BoardSource, Winrock International Institute for Agricultural Development, The National Trust for Historic Preservation, and Vassar College. He is also a board member of the Idyllwild Arts Academy, the Winthrop Rockefeller Charitable Trust, and the Conservation Research Center Foundation in Front Royal, Virginia. Presently, Mr. Dietel is chair of the Pierson-Lovelace Foundation and the Brain Mapping Medical Research Organization at the UCLA Medical School, both in Los Angeles, and the Child Care and Learning Center in Washington, Virginia. He is the founding chair of the American Friends of the British Museum and the American Farmland Trust in Washington, D.C. Mr. Dietel is a member of the executive committee of the Institute for Philanthropy in London.
William M. Dietel has combined careers in educational, philanthropic, and nonprofit sector leadership, spanning more than 40 years.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated to the Rockefeller Archive Center by William M. Dietel.
- Accession 1, 1969-1970, 1973-1990
  - Africa Growth Fund, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Africa News Service, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - American Energy Assurance Council, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - American Farmland Trust, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - American Public Radio, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 5-7)
  - Better World Society, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - British Institute of the United States, 1986-1988 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Center for Community Change, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 10-11)
  - Center for Study of Vietnam Generation, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Colonial Williamsburg Foundation, Board and Committee Agendas, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Colonial Williamsburg Foundation, Annual Reports, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Colonial Williamsburg Foundation, Reports, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Colonial Williamsburg Foundation, Board and Committee Meetings, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Colonial Williamsburg Foundation, Reports, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 17-18)
  - Board of Trustees, Lists and Affiliations, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Conservation Foundation, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Consultative Group on Biological Diversity, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 21-22)
  - Council on Foundations, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Dietel, William M., Chronological File, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - De Rance, Inc., 1977-1984, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - De Rance Foundation, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Foundation for the Development of Polish Agriculture, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - International Fund for Agricultural Research, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Loomis Chaffe School, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - National Association of Independent Schools, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - National Audubon Soicety, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Cliveden of the National Trust, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - National Trust for Historic Preservation, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - National Trust for Historic Preservation, 1985-1988 (Box 5, Folder 34-38)
  - Heritage Trust, 1985, 1987-1989 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - New York Public Library, 1987-1989 (Box 6, Folder 40-41)
  - New York Regional Association of Grantmakers, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Pittsburgh Foundation, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Pocantico Institute, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 44-45)
  - Pocantico Estate, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 46-48)
  - Fund for Private Assistance in International Development (PAID), 1987 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Queen Elizabeth House, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Rockefeller, David, Jr., 1987 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Royal Academy of Trust, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Sleepy Hollow Restoration, Inc., 1987 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - South Africa, General, 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 54-58)
  - Southern African Advanced Education Project, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Southern African Centre for Cooperation in Agricultural Research, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Synergos Institute, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 61-62)
  - WETA, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - Winthrop Rockefeller Charitable Trust, 1975-1976, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - Winthrop Rockefeller CharitableTrust, 1985-1987, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 65-66)
    - Winthrop Rockefeller Charitable Trust, 1985-1987, 1989
      Separated Materials
      Oversized chart
  - Winrock International, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 67-70)
  - Winrock International, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 71-75)
  - Winrock International, Annual Reports, 1979-1984 (Box 11, Folder 76)
  - Winrock International, Annual and Other Reports, 1982, 1985-1987 (Box 12, Folder 77)
  - Winrock International, Nominating Committee, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 78)
  - Winrock International, Project Summary Statements, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 79)
  - Winrock International, Board of Directors Meeting, 1986 April 15-16 (Box 12, Folder 80)
  - World Resources Institute, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 81)
  - Zero Bond Fund, 1986-1988 (Box 12, Folder 82)
  - Nitrogen Fixing Tree Association, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 83)
  - Nitrogen Fixing Tree Association, Annual Meeting, 1988 February 21-24 (Box 12, Folder 84)
  - American Public Radio, Inc., Board of Directors, 1986 June 27 (Box 12, Folder 85)
  - Weekly Appointment Book, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 86)
  - National Trust for Historic Preservation, Committees, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 87)
  - National Trust for Historic Preservation, The Trusteeship Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 13, Folder 88-89)
  - National Trust for Historic Preservation, Trustee Briefing Book, 1988-1989 (Box 13, Folder 90-91)
  - National Trust for Historic Preservation, Review of the National Trust's Historic Properties, 1988 January 19 (Box 13, Folder 92)
  - National Trust for Historic Preservation, Resources Development Committee, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 93)
  - Dietel, Williiam M., Biographical Sheet, 1987 April (Box 14, Folder 94)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1978, 1981-1983 (Box 14, Folder 95-99)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1984-1987 (Box 15, Folder 100-104)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 103A)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Restricted from access - Confidential material
  - Day File, 1987 January-March (Box 15, Folder 105)
  - Day File, 1987 April-December (Box 16, Folder 106-108)
  - Memoranda to File, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 109)
  - Wordsworth Trust (Box 16, Folder 110)
  - University Club, 1980-1981, 1983-1987 (Box 16, Folder 111-112)
  - Week at a Glance, Professional Appointments, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 113)
  - International Fund for Agricultural Research (IFAR), 1986-1987 (Box 17, Folder 114)
  - African Trip, 1986-1987 (Box 17, Folder 115)
  - Phone Messages and Memoranda, 1986-1987 (Box 17, Folder 116)
  - Phone Messages and Memoranda, 1986-1987 (Box 17, Folder 116A)
  - Winrock International, 1987-1989 (Box 17, Folder 117-118)
  - Winrock International, Investment Meeting, 1988 February 22 (Box 17, Folder 119)
  - Winrock International, Endowment Campaign and Program Grants, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 120)
  - National Trust for Historic Preservation, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 121)
  - Roberts, Ann, Letter to Laurance S. Rockefeller, Rockefeller Brothers Fund and Rockefeller Family Fund, 1979-1980 (Box 18, Folder 122)
  - Rockefeller Archive Center, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 123)
  - Letters of Recommendation, 1969-1970, 1973-1975, 1977-1987 (Box 18, Folder 124-126)
  - WInthrop Rockefeller Trust, Proposals from Ranch Management Program, 1985-1987 (Box 18, Folder 127)
  - Compensation, 1978-1980, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 128)
    Restricted from access-Personnel
  - John D. Rockefeller 150th Anniversary Celebration, Follow-up Meeting, 1989-1990 (Box 19, Folder 129-130)
  - John D. Rockefeller 150th Anniversary Celebration, Budget, 1989-1990 (Box 19, Folder 131)
  - John D. Rockefeller 150th Anniversary Celebration, Committee Meeting Agendas, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 132)
  - John D. Rockefeller 150th Anniversary Celebration, Background Papers, 1988-1989 (Box 19, Folder 133)
  - John D. Rockefeller 150th Anniversary Celebration, Contributions to Conference, 1989-1990 (Box 19, Folder 134)
  - John D. Rockefeller 150th Anniversary Celebration, Gifts to Delegates, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 135)
  - John D. Rockefeller 150th Anniversary Celebration, Invitees/Delegates, 1989-1990 (Box 19, Folder 136-137)
  - John D. Rockefeller 150th Anniversary Celebration, Invitees/Delegates, 1989-1990 (Box 20, Folder 138)
  - John D. Rockefeller 150th Anniversary Celebration, Speakers and Papers, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 139)
  - John D. Rockefeller 150th Anniversary Celebration, The Birthday Party, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 140)
  - John D. Rockefeller 150th Anniversary Celebration, Contracts, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 141)
  - John D. Rockefeller 150th Anniversary Celebration, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 142)
  - John D. Rockefeller 150th Anniversary Celebration, Media, 1989-1990 (Box 20, Folder 143)
  - John D. Rockefeller 150th Anniversary Celebration, Miscellaneous Notes, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 144)
  - John D. Rockefeller 150th Anniversary Celebration, Program/Schedule of Conference, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 145)
  - John D. Rockefeller 150th Anniversary Celebration, 1989 October 26-29 (Box 20, Folder 146)
  - John D. Rockefeller 150th Anniversary Celebration, 1988-1989 (Box 21, Folder 147-149)
  - John D. Rockefeller 150th Anniversary Celebration, Planning, 1988-1989 (Box 21, Folder 150)
  - John D. Rockefeller 150th Anniversary Celebration, David Rockefeller, Sr., 1988 (Box 21, Folder 151)
- Accession 2, 1982-1993
  - AAFRC Trust for Philanthropy, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 152)
  - Academy of London, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 153)
  - Action Center for Eastern Europe and the Soviet Union (Box 21, Folder 154)
  - African News Service, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 155)
  - Agriculture Council of America, 1988-1989 (Box 21, Folder 156)
  - Allelix, Inc., 1989 (Box 21, Folder 157)
  - American Conservation Association, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 158)
  - American Energy Assurance Council, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 159)
  - American Farm School, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 160)
  - American Farmland Trust, 1987-1988 (Box 21, Folder 161)
  - American Farmland Trust, 1989-1991 (Box 22, Folder 162-164)
  - American Farmland Trust, Reports, 1990-1991 (Box 22, Folder 165)
  - American Friends of British Museum, 1987-1988, 1990-1991 (Box 22, Folder 166)
  - American National Bank, (Poland), 1990 October (Box 22, Folder 167)
  - American Public Radio, 1987-1988, 1990-1991, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 168-171)
  - American Public Radio, 1987-1990 (Box 24, Folder 172-177)
  - American Public Radio, Board of Directors Meeting, 1987 January 16-1988 October 11 (Box 25, Folder 178-182)
  - American Public Radio, Toward a Market-Oriented Strategy, 1987 July (Box 26, Folder 183)
  - American Trust for Agriculture in Poland, 1989-1990 (Box 26, Folder 184-188)
  - American Trust for Agriculture in Poland, 1989-1990 (Box 26, Folder 185A)
  - American Trust for Agriculture in Poland, 1989-1991 (Box 27, Folder 189-193)
  - American Trust for Agriculture in Poland, 1989-1991 (Box 28, Folder 194-195)
  - Barnes Foundation, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 196)
  - Billfish Foundation, 1988-1990 (Box 28, Folder 197)
  - Brown University, 1988-1989 (Box 28, Folder 198)
  - Bryant Park Restoration, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 199)
  - Cambridge College, 1988-1991 (Box 28, Folder 200)
  - Campaign to End Hunger and Homelessness, 1988-1989 (Box 28, Folder 201)
  - Campaign for Oxford, 1987-1992 (Box 28, Folder 202)
  - Carnegie Commission on Science, Technology, and Government, 1990-1991 (Box 28, Folder 203)
  - Carter Center of Emory University, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 204)
  - Center for Community Change, 1987-1991 (Box 29, Folder 205-207)
  - Center for Science Information, 1989-1990 (Box 29, Folder 208)
  - Center for 21st Century, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 209)
  - Center on Philanthropy, 1990-1991 (Box 29, Folder 210)
  - Century Association, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 211)
  - Chasin, Dana, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 212)
  - Citizen Ambassador Program, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 213)
  - Coalition for Essential Schools, 1988, 1990-1991 (Box 30, Folder 214)
  - College of Natural Resources, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 215)
  - Colonial Williamsburg Foundation, 1990-1992 (Box 30, Folder 216-220)
  - Colonial Williamsburg Foundation, 1988-1992 (Box 31, Folder 221-226)
  - Colonial Williamsburg Foundation, 1988-1990 (Box 32, Folder 227-230)
    - Colonial Williamsburg Foundation, 1988 August 5
      Oversized architectural drawing
  - Colonial Williamsburg Foundation, Nominating Committee, 1988 November 11 (Box 32, Folder 231)
  - Colonial Williamsburg Foundation, Board and Committee Agendas, 1988 November 11-12 (Box 32, Folder 232)
  - Conservation Foundation, 1987-1990 (Box 33, Folder 233)
  - The Conservation Fund, 1989-1990 (Box 33, Folder 234)
  - Consultative Group on Biological Diversity, 1987-1991 (Box 33, Folder 235-237)
  - Cornell University, Center for International Studies, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 238)
  - Cornell Institute for Food & Agriculture Development, 1988-1990 (Box 33, Folder 239-240)
  - Cornell University, 1988-1989, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 242-243)
  - Cornell University, College of Human Ecology, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 244)
  - Cornell Institute for Food & Agriculture Development, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 241)
  - Cornell University, Center for international Studies, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 245)
  - Curry Foundation, 1989 (Box 34, Folder 246)
  - Council on Environmental Affairs, Paul Growald, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 247)
  - Council on Foreign Relations, 1989-1992 (Box 34, Folder 248)
  - Cultural Literacy Foundation, 1989-1990 (Box 34, Folder 249)
  - Dublin City University Trust, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 250)
  - Earthwatch, 1989, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 251)
  - EcoVentures, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 252)
  - European Foundation Center, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 253)
  - Geraldine R. Dodge Foundation, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 254)
  - Fannie Mae, 1988-1989 (Box 35, Folder 255)
  - Farm Foundation, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 256)
  - Foreign Student Service Council, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 257)
  - Ford Foundation, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 258)
  - Foundation Common Fund, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 259)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), 1989-1990 (Box 35, Folder 260-264)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), 1989-1990 (Box 36, Folder 265-268)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), Norman Borlaug, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 269)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), Nominating Committee, 1992 (Box 36, Box 270)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 37, Folder 271)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), Council Members, 1989-1993 (Box 37, Folder 272)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), Board Members, 1990-1993 (Box 37, Folder 273-274)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), 1992 (Box 37, Folder 275)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), Board Meetings, 1989-1992 (Box 37, Folder 276)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), Council Meetings, 1988, 1990-1992 (Box 38, Folder 277)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), 1988-1990 (Box 38, Folder 278-279)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), U. S. Government Contacts, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 280)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), Publications/Papers, 1988-1989 (Box 38, Folder 281)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), American Express Project on Tourism, 1992 (Box 38, Folder 282)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), Credit Agreement, Meat Processing, 1988, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 283)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), Institute of Sustainable Development, 1992 (Box 38, Folder 284)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), Pig Project, 1992-1993 (Box 38, Folder 285)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), Women's Project, 1992 (Box 38, Folder 286)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), Inforum, 1991-1992 (Box 38, Folder 287)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), Projects, 1990-1993 (Box 39, Folder 288)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), Telecommunications Projects, 1990-1991 (Box 39, Folder 289)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), European Community, 1991-1992 (Box 39, Folder 290)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), Background Reading, 1989-1992 (Box 39, Folder 291-292)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), Polish Personalities, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 293)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), Dinner at the University Club, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 294)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), Josef Ertl, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 295)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), Gill Whittington, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 296)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), Annual reports, 1988-1989 (Box 39, Folder 297)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), Current News About Poland, 1988-1991 (Box 40, Folder 298-299)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), Ron McCreery, 1991-1993 (Box 40, Folder 300-301)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), Ron McCreery, Contracts, 1991 (Box 40, Folder 302)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), Ron McCreery Evaluations, 1992 (Box 40, Folder 303)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), Greg Vaut, 1992 (Box 40, Folder 304)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), Greg Vaut's Contacts, 1989-1991 (Box 41, Folder 305)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), Executive Director Search, 1990-1991 (Box 41, Folder 306)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), Trix Smalley, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 307)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), Compensation, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 308)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), Compensation, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 308A)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), Bob Bose, 1989-1992 (Box 41, Folder 309)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), Judith Symonds, 1991-1992 (Box 41, Folder 310)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), Budget, 1989-1990, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 311)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), Development European, 1991-1992 (Box 41, Folder 312)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), Development U. S., 1991, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 313)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), Development and Planning Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 42, Folder 314)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), Plan 1992-1993 (Box 42, Folder 315)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), Staff, 1990-1993 (Box 42, Folder 316)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), Legal Matters, 1991-1992 (Box 42, Folder 317)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), Invoices, 1990 (Box 42, Folder 318)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), Winrock Contract, 1990, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 319)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), Joint Commission, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 320)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), Business Plan (Box 42, Folder 321)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), CARESBAC, 1990-1992 (Box 42, Folder 322)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), Investments, 1991, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 323)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), Polish-American Enterprise Fund, 1990, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 324)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), Agri-Services Company, 1990, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 325)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), Aid Proposal, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 326)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), Monthly Reports, 1990-1993 (Box 42, Folder 327)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), Press Releases, 1990 (Box 42, Folder 328)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), Polish Law on Foundations, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 329)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), Travel Expense Report, 1988 (Box 42, Folder 330)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), Organization, 1988-1992 (Box 42, Folder 331)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), Organization, 1988-1992 (Box 43, Folder 332)
  - Foundation for Development of Polish Agriculture (FDPA), Employment Candidates, 1988-1990 (Box 43, Folder 333)
  - Global Warming, Coordinating Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 43, Folder 334)
  - Good Dirt, 1990 (Box 43, Folder 335)
  - Grand Canyon Trust, 1989 (Box 43, Folder 336)
  - Hampshire College, 1988, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 337)
  - Harkness Fellowships, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 338)
  - Heritage Trust, 1988 (Box 43, Folder 339)
  - Historic Hudson Valley, 1988-1990 (Box 43, Folder 340-341)
  - Historic Hudson Valley, 1988-1990 (Box 44, Folder 342)
  - Historic Hudson Valley, Executive Committee, 1991-1993 (Box 44, Folder 343-344)
  - Historic Hudson Valley, Finance Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 44, Folder 345)
  - Historic Hudson Valley, Development Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 44, Folder 346)
  - Historic Hudson Valley, John Dobkin, 1991-1992 (Box 44, Folder 347)
  - Historic Hudson Valley, The Cambridge Study, 1989-1990 (Box 44, Folder 348)
  - Historic Hudson Valley, Mission Statement, 1989 (Box 45, Folder 349)
  - Historic Hudson Valley, 1988-1990 (Box 45, Folder 350-351)
  - Historic Hudson Valley, A. J. Davis and American Classicism, 1989 (Box 45, Folder 352)
  - Historic Hudson Valley, Draft Study for a Hudson Valley Greenway, 1990 April (Box 45, Folder 353)
  - Historic Hudson Valley, Montgomery Place Plan, 1989 (Box 45, Folder 354)
  - Historic Hudson Valley, Hudson River Valley Greenway, 1990 (Box 45, Folder 355)
  - Historic Hudson Valley, Vista Report for Montgomery Place, 1989 February 1 (Box 45, Folder 356)
  - Historic Hudson Valley, 1988 Financial Review, 1989 January 30 (Box 45, Folder 357)
  - Historic Hudson Valley, Adjourned Annual Meeting and Board of Trustees, 1987 December 4 (Box 45, Folder 358)
  - Historic Hudson Valley, Annual Meeting and Board of Trustees, 1988 June 10 (Box 45, Folder 359)
  - Historic Hudson Valley, Adjourned Annual Meeting and Board of Trustees, 1988 December 2 (Box 46, Folder 360)
  - Historic Hudson Valley, Annual Meeting and Board of Trustees, 1989 March 21 (Box 46, Folder 361)
  - Historic Hudson Valley, Adjourned Annual Meeting, 1989 September 22 (Box 46, Folder 362)